https://www.cdiglobal.com/en/privacy-policy

Login
Our Firm
Why CDI?
Retail
Technology, Media & Telecommunications (TMT)
Our Firm
CDI Global provides middle-market advisory with globalreaching success. Our commitment is to deliver worldclass service built on long-term client relationships. Our international reach and core values drive our history of successful cross-border transactions.
Why CDI?
CDI Global is a leading international middle-market advisory firm, specializing in strategic cross-border transactions.
History
Established in Brussels, Belgium in 1973, CDI Global was created to serve the middle market.
Leadership
CDI Global is known for our strong leadership, comprised of top industry professionals, entrepreneurs and financial experts across the world.
Locations
CDI Global has offices in more than 40 major financial centers in over 30 countries around the world.
Careers
Our firm is continually evolving and growing, and we are always interested in talented individuals looking to join our team.
Services
CDI Global is a leader in middle-market, cross-border transactions. Our international presence, industry expertise, and market command ensure our ability to help you reach your goals.
Mergers & Acquisitions
CDI Global has strategically advised companies on mergers and acquisitions (M&A) worldwide for almost 50 years.
Mergers
We provide guidance throughout the merger process, from identifying the right fit to addressing any specific challenges, ensuring our clients reach their strategic goals.
Acquisitions
CDI Global is highly experienced in helping our clients make acquisitions of other companies, both cross-border and cross-industry.
Cross-Border Transactions
CDI Global’s network of offices spans more than 30 countries, giving us competitive advantage in facilitating cross-border transactions.
Joint Ventures
In joint ventures, the right fit is key. CDI Global has the international reach and market expertise to find and negotiate strategic alliances.
Company Search
CDI Global provides the active and focused search needed to target acquisitions that fit your company objectives.
Transaction Support
CDI provides full-service mergers and acquisitions transaction support including valuations, due-diligence, and closing support.
Divestitures
CDI Global specializes in divestitures, generating successful exits for private owners, corporations, and private equity backed enterprises alike.
Divestiture Strategy
Our company partnerships and industry expertise are key in developing the best divestiture strategy for our clients.
Broad Auction
CDI Global has an extensive network of connections to ensure maximum exposure for broad auction bidding.
Limited Auction
Our middle-market expertise and industry knowledge delivers the optimal group of prospective and interested buyers to boost limited auction valuations.
Transaction Support
CDI Global provides both transaction support and due diligence while acting as project manager, so our clients can continue running their businesses.
Capital Raising
CDI Global’s extensive experience and relationships within the investment banking community ensure capital raising success.
Corporate Finance Advisory
Our corporate finance advisory planning and strategies come from decades of investment banking and industry CFO experience.
Growth Capital
We help you grow your company by facilitating access to growth capital and guiding you through strategic decisions during the capital raising process.
Recapitalizations
CDI Global guides you through strategic changes in your company’s capital structure and maximizes opportunities.
Management Buyout
We are highly experienced at guiding companies through the complex financing a management buyout (MBO) entails.
Leveraged Buyout
CDI Global’s extensive financial experience can facilitate a smooth leveraged buyout (LBO) with optimal term negotiations.
Representative Transactions
Industries
CDI Global comprises international advisory teams with mergers and acquisitions experience in many key industries.
Aerospace
Within the Aerospace and Defense Industry sector, CDI Global has experienced and dedicated partners who can identify and interview appropriate candidates on a face-to-face basis.
Automotive
The Automotive Industry forecast is still favorable due to the development of new technologies, spurring an increase of cross-border and cross-sector opportunities.
Chemicals
CDI Global’s knowledge and experience in the Chemicals Industry sector includes coatings, adhesives and sealants, polymers and resins, pharmaceuticals and fine chemicals, plastics, surfactants, as well many other product segments.
Energy, Utilities, Mining, Oil & Gas
CDI Global has completed many search-and-sell mandates in the Energy, Utilities and Mining, and Oil and Gas industries. Our global industry experts, as well as country partners in Asia, Europe, and America, constitute our base from which we compose our global search teams.
Fashion & Leisure
The Fashion and Leisure industry includes wearable fashion and retail accessories, as well as beauty products, fragrances, and personal care items. At CDI Global, our team of experts draw upon their decades of experience working across borders to consult and strategize the best available deals and entry points.
Financial Institutions
Our team of experts at CDI Global have decades of combined banking and Financial Institutions experience. This is key to delivering the best results from cross-border mergers and acquisitions as well as debt and equity transactions.
Food & Agriculture
CDI Global has extensive knowledge of the dynamic and innovative changes occurring in the global Food and Agriculture Industry and the insight to advise on complex M&A deals and fundraisings as well as provide comprehensive corporate financial services.
Healthcare, Pharmaceutical & Biotechnology
CDI Global has a proven track record of 80+ healthcare transactions closed by partners, including sell, buy, fund raising, joint ventures, and mergers and acquisitions in all segments and across the globe.
Household Goods
Our CDI Global team brings decades of experience consulting on Household Goods mergers and acquisitions. We understand how to navigate the ever-changing industry to uncover opportunities that match client objectives in this industry.
Industrial, Manufacturing and Services
At CDI Global, our team provides years of experience in transactional execution in the Industrial Services sector. We understand the niche markets and channels, as well as the key global regions, to find and secure the best possible opportunities.
Infrastructure, Construction & Materials
At CDI Global, our professional team has local and global experience of the broad Infrastructure market and seeks to specifically explore those segments that lend themselves to cross border M&A.
Packaging
CDI Global’s team of Packaging experts and dealmakers have the experience to catch trends, account for shifting economic times, and discover new growth opportunities within the industry.
Retail
Our CDI Global team brings decades of experience consulting on Retail mergers and acquisitions. We understand how to navigate the ever-changing industry to discover key opportunities that match our clients’ goals in this sector.
Technology, Media & Telecommunications (TMT)
CDI Global has years of experience in transactional execution among its international team members in the Technology, Media and Telecommunications industries. We understand the niche markets and channels, as well as the key global regions, to find and secure the best possible opportunities.
News / Insights
Contact Us
Resources
CDI Global Members
ESOP Financing
We can help you set up and take strategic advantage of ESOP financing benefits, both to the company and employees.
Partner Portal
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
Back
Our Commitment
CDI Global is committed to earning and keeping the trust of clients, business partners and others who visit our site or share personal information with us. We take your trust and privacy seriously and comply with all applicable privacy and data protection laws.
Our Policy
This policy details how we may use the information we collect about you, as well as your rights over any personal information we may store. CDI Global protects the privacy of our clients and website visitors. We will collect, use and store your personal data in a secure way and only use it for the specific purpose stated.
User Consent
By using a CDI Global internet site or providing personal information, you are consenting to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information as described in this policy.
Marketing
With your permission, CDI Global would like to send you marketing information about our products and services. You may opt-out of receiving these messages by clicking the unsubscribe link located in each email or by emailing privacy@cdiglobal.com.
Cookie Policy
Cookies are small, usually randomly encoded, text files that help you navigate through a website. They are generated on all sites, as well as by third-parties that websites work with, to manage key elements of website functionality. In most cases, they do not involve or use personal information in any way.
You have the ability to accept or decline the use of cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser settings to decline all cookies, or configure your browser to notify you each time a cookie is added. If you chose to decline cookies from CDI Global’s website, your user experience may be impacted.
We work with carefully selected third parties for website tracking and analytics. We use Google Analytics which tracks a website page visitor’s activity and other anonymous information. You may opt-out of Google Analytics tracking on all websites that use it by installing the Google Analytics opt-out add-on to your browser.
In addition to Google Analytics, we use a third party marketing software to track visitor activity. The information tracked may include your IP (internet protocol) address, your web browser, the time you visited the site, webpages visited and other data. You may opt-in or opt-out of this tracking at any time. When you first came to our site, you were prompted to opt-in or opt-out of tracking and the applicable cookie was added to your web browser. That cookie will remain on your browser until deleted. You may change your opt-in/opt-out status at any time by deleting your web browser cookies and selecting again up your return to our site.
Personal Information
CDI Global collects information visitors knowingly and voluntarily provide when using CDI Global internet site. Examples of such information include data provided while completing a website form, signing up for a mailing list, subscribing to our blog, completing surveys, or sending CDI Global emails with questions or feedback. CDI Global uses the personal information only for the purpose for which the user provided it.
CDI Global may store the personal information of current and former customers, business partners, and those we have a legitimate business interest in. We only store the information necessary for the stated business purpose and remove data from our database when we no longer have legitimate business reason to maintain.
Some or all of your data may be stored or transferred outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). If we do store or transfer your data outside of the EEA, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated as safely or securely as it would within the EEA and under GDPR.
You have the right to request a copy of what personal information, if any, CDI stores for you. You may also request that we correct or remove your information. To request a copy of the information or to request to be removed, email privacy@cdiglobal.com. Please note that we cannot delete your information if we are required by law to store it or it is necessary to fulfill a legal contract with you or your company.
Links to Third Party Websites
Our sites may provide links to third party sites that are not operated by CDI Global. These links are provided as a service and do not imply any endorsement of the activities or content of these sites, nor any association with their operators. CDI Global assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites a visitor is able to access through ours, and encourages visitors to review each site’s privacy policy before disclosing any personally identifying information.
This privacy policy only covers the CDI Global website and as such external links are not covered by this policy.
Technology, Media & Telecommunications (TMT)
Connect with a CDI Expert. Request a Call Back.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. Click here for more information.
Allow cookies
